Akash Vedpathak

Business Analyst

av703079@gmail.com

09028661240

Ravet, Pune, India, Pune, India

linkedin.com/in/akash-vedpathak-051287178

github.com/AkashVedpathak

Currently working as a Business Analyst in Zomato Limited. Experienced in handling large datasets, data wrangling and data visualization. Excellent analytical, organizational, and decision-making abilities and motivated to learn, grow and excel in the Data science industry.

EDUCATION

Data Science Program

Edyoda

12/2006 - Present

MBA - Marketing MIT World Peace University, Pune

05/2020 - 05/2022

8.3 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate-Ops WNS Global Services, Pune

04/2019 - 03/2020

- Responsibilities:
- Worked varied hours to meet seasonal and business
- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns
- Cross-trained and provided backup support for organizational leadership
- Evaluated interactions between associates and customers to assess personnel performance

Business Analyst Zomato Limited, Pune

01/2022 - Present

- Responsibilities:
- Collecting and recording data, analyzing data and evaluating and presenting data solutions
- Fetching large datasets from databases using Mysql
- Preparing reports and presenting project results to key stakeholders and clients

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Food ordering app replica (09/2022 - 12/2022)

Designed an app with differential Admin and User functionalities using Python

Library Management system (10/2022 - 12/2022)

Designed an app with differential Admin and User functionalities using Python

CERTIFICATES

Python Certification (06/2022 - 09/2022)

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi Full Professional Proficiency